ANASTASIIA BASHKATOVA

UX/UI DESIGNER

CONTACT

www.bashkatova.design

□ anastasiia.bash@gmail.com

% (415) 769 6236

San Diego, CA

PROFILE

UX/UI Designer with 2+ years of experience creating user-centered, holistic solutions that are functional and research-driven. I love to create clean and modern-looking apps and websites designs, and I truly believe that good design is changing the world.

EDUCATION

Master of Science (MS) in Finance

Lincoln University, Oakland, CA 2014 -2016

UX Design Academy

DesignLab 2019

UX Design Certificate

Google Career exp. 2022

SKILLS

Research
Information Architecture
Wireframing
Interaction Design
UI Design
Prototyping
Usability Testing
Data Visualization
Layout
Typography
Branding

TOOLS

Figma / Sketch Adobe Creative Suite InVision / Marvel Miro

WORK EXPERIENCE

UX/UI Designer

3D Room Space Inc.

Jun 2020 - July 2021

- Developed a new information architecture through research, competitive analysis and customer feedback
- Designed App screens for mobile and tablet using tools like Sketch, Illustrator, Photoshop
- Created investor pitch deck that helped to bring investors to the startup
- Collaborated effectively with the marketing and dev teams to increase conversion rate

Graphic Designer | UI Designer

Freelance, Remote

Nov 2019 - 2022

- Designed logos, brand identities and UI/UX of the websites and applications (Android/iOS) adhering to current standards and trends
- Collaborated with the marketing team to redesign the website's inefficient workflows to get a clear and usercentered interface, increasing traffic average by 20%
- Collaborated closely with cross-functional teams in an agile environment to ensure all designs meet both business and users' objectives

Project Engineer

USS Cal Builders

Sep 2015 - Nov 2018

- Determined project specifications by studying product design and submitting documents to project owner through construction management software (Procore)
- Prepare Schedule of Values for the project and monthly payment applications
- Prepared cost estimates, invoices, RFIs and change orders to subcontractors and owners based on negotiations